Chia-Hsin (Joyce) Wang

LPQM. 61 Ave. du Président Wilson, 94230, Cachan, France++33(0)781856520+cwang@ens-cachan.fr

Summary

Varied experience in Biomedical Engineering from clinical examination to medical device. Familiar with microscopy and nanotechnology. Strong communication skills and the ability of solving problems because of several living experience, study in Taiwan, in France and in Poland.

Education

ENS Cachan - École Normale Supérieure de Cachan, Paris, France

Sep. 2013 – Present

M.S., Molecular nano- and bio-photonics for telecommunications and biotechnologies

Relevant Coursework: Molecular Interaction, Microfluidics, Fundamental Molecular Spectroscopy,

Spectroscopic and Chemometric technique, Photon-Induced Electron Transfer.

National Taiwan University Taipei, Taiwan

Sep. 2009 -Jun.2011

M.S., BioMedical Engineering

GPA:3.7/4.0

Relevant Coursework:Medical Microsensor, Medical Device Quality System, Nano-Micro Engineering in Biomedicine, LabVIEW, Matlab, Laser Principle and Engineering

Thesis – Two-Photon Excitation Fluorescence Correlation Spectroscopy for Green Fluorescent Protein in Human Embryonic Kidney 293 Cell Cytosol

National Yang Ming University, Taipei, Taiwan

Sep.2004 - Jun.2008

B.S., Biotechnology and Laboratory Science in Medicine

GPA: 3.3/4.0

Publications

C. H. Wang, D. H. Wang, C.W. Lin, Y. S. Kuan, Two photon Fluorescence Correlation Spectroscopy Parameter Analysis for Green Fluorescence Protein, TSBMES 2011 Tainan.

Experience

Fraunhofer Institute For Production Technology, Aachen, Germany

Internship / Master thesis

 $Mar\ 2015-Present$

Design a new platform of Lateral Flow ImmunoAssay

University of Michigan Microsystems Technology and Science Lab, Ann Arbor, MI

Internship

Sep 2014 - Oct 2014

Fabricate microfluidical devices for measuring patient's immunotyping

Mackay Memorial Hospital, Taipei, Taiwan

Medical Technologist

Aug 2008 – Oct 2008

Drew patients' blood and analyzed blood sample, also analyzed urine sediment to make reports to doctors

Mackay Memorial Hospital, Taipei, Taiwan

Medical Technologist Intern

Jul 2007 - Jan 2008

Examined clinical specimens via Biochemistry, Blood Banking, Microbiology, Physiology, Parasitology and Microscopy, Virology, Sereology, Hematology, Diagnosis Cytology, EEG

Skills

Certificate Medical Technologist of Department of Health of Taiwan

Lab skills: Fluorescence microscopy, Two-Photon Excitation Microscopy(TPM), Fluorescence Correlation

Spectroscopy(FCS), Clinical Examination

Awards

Erasmus Mundus Master Full Scholarship 2013-2015

Languages

Mandarin Chinese(Native); English (Intermediate); French (Listening is intermediate)